stocktwits.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy

**Last Revised: January 4, 2018**

Stocktwits, Inc. provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website, located at [https://www.stocktwits.com](https://www.stocktwits.com/) and any other website owned and operated by Stocktwits, Inc. or its affiliates, including moneybadger.stocktwits.com, (each a "Site," and collectively, the "Sites") and any related Stocktwits mobile device application (the "App") or collected through the products and services available at the Sites, (together with the Sites, the "Service" ).

In these this Privacy Policy, "you" or "your" means the person using the Service and the company (if any) on whose behalf he/she is acting, and "we," "us," "our," "Stocktwits," or the "Company" means Stocktwits, Inc. and its affiliates.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

By using the Service you agree to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States.

If you reside outside the U.S., your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the U.S., and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By using the Service and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, the U.S. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [privacy@stocktwits.com](mailto:privacy@stocktwits.com).

## I. Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting personally identifiable information are to provide you with the product and services made available through the Service, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one.

_Information we collect._ We may collect the following categories of personal information about you through the Site, including but not limited to:

  * Registration information: To use certain features of the Services, you will need to register an account. When you make an account, you will be asked for basic registration information, such as an email address and password.
  * Identification information: You may also be asked to provide identification information to confirm your identity, including your first and last name, username, address, and phone number.
  * Third party credentials: You may also enter in certain passwords, usernames, account numbers, and other account information for websites, apps, products or services provided by third-party service providers ("Third-Party Services").
  * Information from Third-Party Services: In order to display information to you through the Service, we may collect, on your behalf, your account and other personal information from Third-Party Services that you register under your account via the Service. For example, if you register your Robinhood or TradeIt account with us, we will aggregate your Robinhood or TradeIt information via our Service in order to present it to you. If you choose to access Robinhood’s or TradeIt’s services through our Service, we may store a representation of your account information including but not limited to account holdings and transaction histories from your Robinhood or TradeIt accounts.
  * Technical and navigational information: We collect information about your interaction with our Site such as computer browser type, pages visited, average time spent on our Site, IP address, unique identifier of the device, operating system version and app version.
  * Location information: If you choose to use a location enabled Service, we may collect location information from your device and will notify you of this collection. You may control or disable the sharing of location information via your device setting and/or the Site.
  * Other information: We may request or receive other personal information such as feedback, questions, comments, suggestions, or ideas to provide you with other benefits or to improve upon the Service. In such instances, you will be given the opportunity to provide or decline that information.

Your full user name and your image (if you decide to upload one) for which you registered on Twitter.com ("Twitter") are displayed to people in the Stocktwits network to enable you to connect with people on Stocktwits, as specified in your privacy settings on Twitter. If you activate the mobile device options, when available, per the Terms of Use at <https://www.stocktwits.com/st/terms>, we will collect your cellular phone number. If you contact us by email through the Site, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you.

_Use of Contact Information._ In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

_Log Data._ When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Service, and for the Service’s technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Use.

_Do Not Track._ We do not respond to web browser "do not track" or other related mechanisms at this time.

## II. Cookies

Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. Stocktwits may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Service, to serve ads on the Service that are tailored to your interests, and to improve the Service. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our Service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

## III. Information Sharing and Disclosure

_Service Providers._ We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data. In addition, we may use information you provide about Third-Party Services to provide the Service, which may include accessing the Third-Party Services you select on your behalf, so that we can present the requested information to you. With respect to mobile applications or mobile versions of our Sites, we may collect the unique device identifier assigned to that device by phone makers, carriers, or makers of the operating system (the "Device ID"). Device IDs allow app developers, advertisers, and others to uniquely identify your device for purposes of storing application preferences and other data.

We may use your Device ID for security purposes. For example, if you have activated a feature that limits access to a Service from a specific device, our systems will access the Device ID from each device you attempt to access the Service with to determine if the device is the specific authorized device. Additionally, we may use Device IDs to monitor suspicious activity. For example, if we detect that a single account on a Site is being accessed from multiple devices, as determined by tracking the Device IDs that access an account, we may contact the user to ensure that such access has been authorized by the user.

_Google Analytics._ We may also use web analytics services hosted by third parties, such as Google Analytics.

Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users interact with the Service. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to, and stored by, Google on their servers. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Service, compiling reports on website activity for us and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Service. By using the Service, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

_Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement._ Stocktwits cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Stocktwits or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

_Business Transfers._ Stocktwits may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

_Personal Information._ Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we will not, without your permission, sell, publish, or share your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes.

In connection with third party services, we may share some of your personal information with the third parties when you are attempting to process the transaction you have requested.

We may share your personal information with third party service providers to enable them to assist in fulfilling the requests you make or the transactions you conduct via the Sites, including the operation of certain Site functions and Services. Third parties acting on our behalf that are given access to your personal information are contractually obligated to abide by our privacy practices and are not allowed to use the information for any other purposes.

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to share or disclose your personal information with law enforcement, government officials, and other third parties:

  * to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process;
  * in order to investigate, prevent, defend against, or take other action regarding violations of our Terms of Service, illegal activities, suspected fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the legal rights or physical safety of any person or the security of our network, Sites or Services;
  * to respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third parties;
  * in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of our Sites' users or the general public; or
  * as otherwise required by any applicable law.

We may share your personal information with other third parties with your consent or instructions to do so.

## IV. Advertising

_Ad Serving._ We may serve ads on the Service. Such ads may be delivered to you by a web advertising vendor. In order to serve ads to you, we may use information collected during your searches or visits to our websites and information that we specifically acquire from third parties.

_Advertising and Cookies._ Some of our third party advertising partners may distribute cookies to users in advertisements that are provided to us. Stocktwits has no access to or control over these cookies once we have received the advertisements. Some of these advertisers and services we use to deliver advertising may be engaging in online behavioral advertising as defined by the Digital Advertising Alliance and FTC.

_Affiliate Advertising._ We participate in affiliate advertising and allow affiliate links to be encoded on some of our pages. This means that we may earn a commission when you click on or make purchases via affiliate links and affiliate partners may use cookies to understand your use of the Services.

Although Stocktwits does not provide any Personally Identifiable Information to third-party advertising companies, if an advertiser asks Stocktwits to show an advertisement to users with certain characteristics or a segment of that group (for example, men ages 21-30 who have viewed certain categories of content on the Service) and you respond to that advertisement, the third-party advertising company may conclude that you have the characteristics of the audience that they are trying to reach.

_Opt-out._ As part of our commitment to transparency and your privacy, we provide the following links to opt-out of cookies provided by both our first party ad server and many third party advertising partners who may be engaging in online behavioral advertising:

_First Party Opt-out._ Please visit this link to opt-out of cookies from our first party ad serving vendor, Google: <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>; Third Party and Online Behavioral Advertising Opt-out – Please visit this link to opt-out of cookies from over 50+ major third party behavioral advertising providers: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

_Interest-Based Advertising Opt-out._ We or third parties may serve ads on the Service that are tailored to your interests and based on your activity online or in the applications on your mobile device. This type of ad tailoring — sometimes called "interest-based" or "online behavioral" advertising — is enabled through various technologies, including browser cookies, mobile advertising identifiers as well as other non-cookie technologies. Information we collect subject to this Privacy Policy may be used for interest-based advertising, and may be shared with our service providers or partners for the purpose of serving such tailored ads. In particular, we and our service providers and partners may use cookies and information you may provide during the registration process or otherwise enter when populating your profile, such as the type of investments that interest you. To opt-out of interest-based advertising please visit [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/](), where you may change your browser settings to no longer be shown ads that have been tailored to your interests.

## V. Third Party Data Collection

We may offer a number of separate products and services offered by third parties advertised by you on our Site and through the Service. These third party offers may be complementary to your use of the Site and may be personalized based on information you provide to us, we have collected about you, queries made through the Site, or other information. If you choose to use these separate products and services, provide information to the third party, or allow the third party to otherwise collect information about you, then their use of your information is subject to the applicable third party’s privacy policy and terms of service. You should review the practices of the third party before deciding to use their service, provide us any of your information with respect to the third party or provide them with any information. Please be aware that Stocktwits is not responsible for the privacy practices of any third party’s privacy practices.

You should also be aware that some content delivered through the Service originates with third parties. Such other content providers may place cookies on your computer, or otherwise gather information about you, including by asking you to provide information through the content player itself. Again, it is up to you to review the terms of use and privacy policy of the originators of such content.

## VI. Security

Stocktwits is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, but we cannot and do not assure that these measures will be sufficient to protect against all efforts to gain unauthorized access to the information.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site.

## VII. Links to Other Websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

## VIII. Our Policy Towards Children

The Site is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [parents@stocktwits.com](mailto:parents@stocktwits.com). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.

## IX. California Privacy Rights

California law permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at [support@stocktwits.com](mailto:support@stocktwits.com).

## X. Access and Deletion Rights

You have the right to access, correct or delete Personal Information held about you by Stocktwits. To the extent allowed, any requests to exercise such rights may be subject to a small fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the Personal Information we hold about you. Should you wish to access the Personal Information held about you, please let us know by contacting us at the contact information provided below.

To request access to personal data relating to you which is processed by Stocktwits, and/or if you have any questions about the handling of personal information, please send an email to [support@stocktwits.com](mailto:support@stocktwits.com).
